Guide to the Johan Kugelberg hip hop collection, circa 1975-1985, 2008.
Kugelberg, Johan hip hop collection,
- Series I. Sound Recordings (1-24)
  - LPs - SR 155-205 (Box 4)
    - Disconet program service Volume 4, program 12 Performed by: Various performers, ca. 1985; SR-191 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Disconet
      Track listing: Just can't get enough (extended remix) (Depeche Mode) -- Stop ou encore (Plastic Bertrand) -- Dance, it's my life (vocal version) (Midnight Powers) -- Don't turn your back on love (extended remix) (Eloise Whitaker) -- It's good to be queen/West Texas rap (Sylvia & Casey Jones) -- Casey Jones' eurodance medley 2. Flash in the night (Secret Service); You gotta problem (Toni Basil); The girls are back in town (Risque); To have and have not (Ronny).
    - To the max instrumental; To the max / Rickey G & the Everloving Five Performed by: Rickey G, 1983; SR-192 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Capo Records
      Track listing: To the max instrumental -- To the max.
    - Funk box party / Masterdon Committee Performed by: Masterdon Committee, 1983; SR-193 (Box 4)
      Track listing: Funk box party -- Funk box party.
    - Fantasy; Betcha don't / Satin Performed by: Satin, 1980; SR-194 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Karousell Records
      Track listing: Fantasy (radio mix) -- Fantasy (club mix) -- Betcha don't (radio mix) -- Betcha don't (club mix).
    - Rap-o clap-o; El rap-o clap-o / Joe Bataan Performed by: Joe Bataan, 1979; SR-195 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Salsoul Records
      Track listing: Rap-o clap-o -- El rap-o clap-o.
    - Rap-o clap-o / Joe Bataan Performed by: Joe Bataan, 1980; SR-196 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Salsoul Record Corp.
      Track listing: Mestizo suite (Mestizo, Rap-o clap-o, Sadie [she smokes]) -- Latin lover -- Mestizo medley (Rock me all night long, I see your hiney, Rap-o dance-o) -- Always and forever.
    - Big throwdown / Johnny Dynell and New York 88 Performed by: Johnny Dynell, 1983; SR-197 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Acme Music
      Track listing: The big throwdown (club version) -- The big throwdown (radio version) -- The big throwdown (live wire boogie dub) -- The big throwdown (J.D.'s revenge).
    - Once upon a time / John Rocca Performed by: John Rocca, vocals; with vocal and instrumental acc, 1984; SR-198 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Streetwise
      Track listing: Once upon a time -- Once upon a time (radio edit) -- Once upon a dub -- Once upon a beatbox.
    - Jam to remember (disco mix & breaks) / Just Four; Jam to remember (hip hop mix & breaks) / Just Four; Instrumental version / Grand Groove Bunch Performed by: Just Four, ca. 1985; SR-199 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Grand Groove Records
      Track listing: Jam to remember (disco mix & breaks) (Just Four) -- Jam to remember (hip hop mix & breaks) (Just Four) -- Instrumental version (Grand Groove Bunch).
    - Exorcist sound; Play me / the Kid's Production Performed by: Kid's Production, 1981; SR-200 (Box 4)
      Track listing: Exorcist sound -- Play me.
    - Rhythm talk; Ain't no stoppin' us now (instrumental) / Jocko Performed by: Jocko, vocals; with instrumental acc, 1979; SR-201 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Philadelphia International Records
      Track listing: Rhythm talk -- Ain't no stoppin' us now (instrumental).
    - Rhythm talk; Ain't no stoppin' us now (instrumental) / Jocko Performed by: Jocko, 1979; SR-202 (Box 4)
    - Bubble bunch / Jimmy Spicer Performed by: Jimmy Spicer, 1982; SR-203 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Mercury
      Track listing: The bubble bunch (vocal) -- The bubble bunch (inst.).
    - Adventures of super rhyme (rap) / Jimmy Spicer Performed by: Jimmy Spicer, 1980; SR-204 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Dazz Records
      Track listing: Adventures of super rhyme (rap) -- Adventures of super rhyme (rap).
    - Rock attack; No wonder (Rock attack instrumental) / J Griffin Performed by: J. Griffin, 1982; SR-205 (Box 4)
      Publisher: Tashamba Records
      Track listing: Rock attack -- No wonder (Rock attack instrumental).
  - LPs - SR 206-259 (Box 5)
    - Smokin' cheeba-cheeba / Harlem Underground Band; Bra / Cymande Performed by: Harlem Underground, ca. 1980; SR-206 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Smokin' cheeba-cheeba (Harlem Underground Band) -- Bra (Cymande).
    - Who is he and what is he to you / Creative Source; Finger in it / Harlem Underground Band Performed by: Creative Source, ca. 1975; SR-207 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Who is he and what is he to you (Creative Source) -- Finger in it (Harlem Underground Band).
    - Shake 'em up / Higher Ground Performed by: Higher Ground, 1981; SR-208 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Shake 'em up (vocal) -- Shake 'em up (instrumental).
    - Cold wind-madness; The coldest rap / Ice T Performed by: Ice-T, 1983; SR-209 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Saturn Records
      Track listing: Cold wind-madness -- The coldest rap.
    - Super rappin' no. 2; Super rappin' theme / Grand Master Flash and the Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, 1980; SR-210 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Super rappin' no. 2 -- Super rappin' theme.
    - It's nasty (genius of love) / Grand Master Flash & Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, 1981; SR-211 (Box 5)
      Track listing: It's nasty (genius of love (vocal short version) -- It's nasty (genius of love (vocal long version).
    - Birthday party / Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, 1981; SR-212 (Box 5)
      Track listing: The birthday party (vocal) -- The birthday party (instrumental).
    - Message / Grand Master Flash & the Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, 1982; SR-213 (Box 5)
      Track listing: The message (vocal) -- The message (instrumental).
    - Flash it to the beat / Flash and the Furious Five; Fusion beats vol. 2 Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, ca. 1985; SR-214 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Bozo Meko Records
      Track listing: Flash it to the beat (Flash and the Furious Five) -- Fusion beats vol. 2.
    - It's nasty (genius of love) / Grand Master Flash & the Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, 1981; SR-215 (Box 5)
      Track listing: It's nasty (genius of love) (Grand Master Flash & the Furious Five) -- It's nasty (genius of love) (Grand Master Flash & the Furious Five).
    - Don't stop the rock / Freestyle Performed by: Freestyle, 1981; SR-216 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Music Specialists
      Track listing: Don't stop the rock (Freestyle) -- Don't stop the rock (instrumental) (Freestyle).
    - Turn you on; Groovin / Full Force Performed by: Full Force, 1980; SR-217 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Turn you on -- Groovin.
    - Funky space player / by Keith "Silver Flash" Ferguson Performed by: Keith "Silver Flash" Ferguson, 1983; SR-218 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Silver Flash Funk Records
      Track listing: Funky space player (vocal) -- Funky space player (instrumental).
    - Feelin' hot / Futura Performed by: Futura, 1982; SR-219 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Feelin' hot -- Feelin' hot.
    - Let's have some music now; Hands up / Damacofe Performed by: Damacofe, 1981; SR-220 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Future Records
      Track listing: Let's have some music now -- Hands up.
    - Nasty rock / Garrett's Crew Performed by: Garrett's Crew, 1983; SR-221 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Clockwork Records
      Track listing: Nasty rock (vocal) -- Nasty rock (instrumental).
    - Keep it on / G-Five with Dave Zinkoff Performed by: G-Five, 1983; SR-222 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Novarro Records
      Track listing: Keep it on (vocal) -- Keep it on (instrumental) -- Keep it on (vocal).
    - Chicken scratch; Chicken dub mix / Glen Adams and DJ Freeze Performed by: Glen Adams, 1983; SR-223 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Chicken scratch -- Chicken dub mix.
    - Girls of the world (genius rap & breaks) / the Just Four; Genius girls inst (plus breaks) / Grand Groove Bunch Performed by: Just Four, ca. 1985; SR-224 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Girls of the world (genius rap & breaks) (Just Four) -- Genius girls inst. (plus breaks) (Grand Groove Bunch).
    - MC delight; Hate da game / Grandmaster Caz Performed by: Grandmaster Caz, 2000; SR-225 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Jazz Child Records
      Track listing: MC delight (Casanova's revenge) -- MC delight (instr.) -- MC delight (Parker Lee mix) -- Hate da game (almost radio version) -- Hate da game (long, big, nasty version) -- Hate da game (instr.).
    - American dream / Grandmaster Freshh Performed by: Grandmaster Freshh, ca. 1985; SR-226 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Street Beat Records
      Track listing: De American dream (radio version) -- De American dream (street version).
    - Name game / Shirley Ellis Performed by: Shirley Ellis, vocals with orch, 1965; SR-227 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Congress
      Track listing: The name game -- Don't let go -- Kansas City -- Shy one -- Stardust -- The nitty gritty -- Such a night -- C.C. rider -- I never will forget -- Stagger Lee -- Whisper to me wind -- Bring it on home to me.
    - Erotic moods Performed by: George Benson, guitar; Ann Winley, vocal; Harlem Underground Band, 1978; SR-228 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Erotic moods.--Fed up.--Loose joints.--Overture erotic (Interlude)--Smokin cheeba-cheeba.--Sweet taste of love.
    - Two sides of Laura Lee Performed by: Laura Lee, vocals, 1972; SR-229 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Hot Wax
      Track listing: At last (my love has come along) -- Every little bit hurts -- Guess who I saw today -- Crumbs off the table -- If you can beat me rockin' (you can have my chair) -- Workin' and lovin' together -- Rip off -- When a man loves a woman -- You've got to save me.
    - Trial / Pigmeat Markham Performed by: Dewey "Pigmeat" Markham, 1961; SR-230 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Chess
    - Feelin' bitchy Performed by: Millie Jackson, vocals; with vocal and instrumental acc, 1977; SR-231 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Spring Records
      Track listing: All the way lover -- Lovin' your good thing away -- Angel in your arms -- A little taste of outside love -- You created a monster -- Cheatin' is -- If you're not back in love by Monday -- Feelin' like a woman.
    - Live and uncensored Performed by: Millie Jackson, vocals; with vocal and instrumental acc, 1979; SR-232 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Keep the home fire burnin' -- Logs and thangs -- Put something down on it -- Da ya think I'm sexy? -- Put something down on it (reprise) -- Just when I needed you most -- Phuck u symphony -- What am I waiting for -- I still love you (you still love me) -- All the way lover -- The soaps -- All the way lover (reprise) -- Hold the line -- Be a sweetheart -- Didn't I blow your mind -- Give it up -- A moment's pleasure -- If loving you is wrong (I don't want to be right) -- The rap -- If loving you is wrong (I don't want to be right) (reprise) -- Never change lovers in the middle of the night -- Sweet music man -- It hurts so good -- Sweet music man (reprise).
    - Still caught up Performed by: Millie Jackson, vocals; with vocal and instrumental acc, 1975; SR-233 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Loving arms -- Making the best of a bad situation -- The memory of a wife -- Tell her it's over -- Do what makes you satisified -- You can't stand the thought -- Leftovers -- I still love you.
    - Take my rap please / Steve Gordon & The Kosher Five Performed by: Steve Gordon, 1979; SR-234 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Take my rap ... please (long version) -- Take my rap ... please (short version)
    - Strawberry Shortcake live Performed by: John Braden, 1981; SR-235 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Kid Stuff Records: Distributed by IJE Distributing Inc.
      Track listing: New York, New York -- Make a wish -- Baby face -- Big apple disco -- Celebration -- Strawberry rap -- Flying -- I can hear the music.
    - Greatest hits / Sugar Hill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1984; SR-236 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Rapper's delight -- Kick it live (from 9 to 5) -- Apache -- 8th wonder -- Showdown (featuring Furious Five).
    - Kick it live from 9 to 5 / Sugar Hill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1983; SR-237 (Box 5)
    - 8th wonder / Sugar Hill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1981; SR-238 (Box 5)
      Publisher: SOS Recording
      Track listing: Funk box -- On the money -- 8th wonder -- Apache -- Showdown (featuring Furious Five) -- Giggalo -- Hot hot summer day.
    - 8th wonder / Sugar Hill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1981; SR-239 (Box 5)
    - Jungle rap; Sula / Starwave Performed by: D.J. Michaels, Brad Baker, James Polles, 1980; SR-240 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Starwave Records
    - Bills; Supa-Rap; Dionne's theme Performed by: A. McKenzie, T.C. Anderson, 1980; SR-241 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Nighthawk Records
      Track listing: Bills -- Supa-Rap -- Dionne's theme -- Supa-Rap.
    - Hurby, the love bug presents Super Nature Performed by: Super Nature, 1985; SR-242 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Pop Art Records
      Track listing: The show stoppa (is stupid fresh) (vocal) -- The Show stoppa (is stupid fresh) (instrumental) -- The show stoppa (is stupid fresh) (def mix).
    - Heartbeat rap; Rap your heart out Performed by: Sweet "G", vocals; with instrumental acc, 1981; SR-243 (Box 5)
      Track listing: A heartbeat rap -- Rap your heart out.
    - I believe in the wheel of fortune / Tanya-Paulette Winley Bra / Cymande (Patterson-Scipio) Performed by: Tanya-Paulette Winley, Bra, Cymande (Patterson-Scipio), 1982; SR-244 (Box 5)
    - Sequential groove / Tidee-T Performed by: Tidi, 1984; SR-245 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Clever Carrere
      Track listing: Sequential groove -- Unlimited dance sounds.
    - "You're hot" / Times Square Performed by: Times Square, 1981; SR-246 (Box 5)
      Publisher: New York City Records
    - Take the city with you / Tin Pan Apple/After Dark Performed by: Tin Pan Apple/After Dark, 1982; SR-247 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Parallel Communications
    - Tongue twistin' ten: TTT Performed by: Tongue twistin' ten, 1983; SR-248 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Earthtone Record Company
      Track listing: Life is a rock (but the radio rolled me) / Norman Dolph and Paul di Franco -- Beat the devil / Adam Ippolito/Mickey Turntable.
    - Street Noise, Trans-Lux Performed by: Trans-Lux, 1983; SR-249 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Master Mix Records
      Track listing: Big Apple noise -- Street noise.
    - Feel the heartbeat (Have fun) / Tre[a]cherous Three Performed by: Treacherous Three, 1981; SR-250 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Feel the heartbeat -- Feel the heartbeat (instrumental)
    - Gotta rock; Turn it up / Treacherous Three Performed by: Treacherous Three, 1985; SR-251 (Box 5)
    - Turning you on; UFO Performed by: Treacherous Three and Tom Tom Club, 1983; SR-252 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Turning you on -- U.F.O.
    - Action / Treacherous Three Performed by: Treacherous Three, 1983; SR-253 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Action (vocal) -- Action (instrumental).
    - Feel the heartbeat / Treacherous Three Performed by: Treacherous Three, 1980; SR-254 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Feel the heartbeat (vocal) -- Feel the heartbeat (instrumental) / Pumpkin & Friends.
    - Johnny the Fox / Tricky Tee Performed by: Tricky Tee, 1985; SR-255 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Sleeping Bag
      Track listing: Johnny the Fox -- Johnny the Fox (Bonus beats) -- Johnny the Fox (Radio version).
    - Cut it up / Tski Valley Performed by: T Ski Valley, ca. 1975; SR-256 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Grand Groove
      Track listing: Cut it up -- Cut it up (instrumental)
    - Sexual rapping / T Ski Valley Performed by: T Ski Valley, ca. 1985; SR-257 (Box 5)
      Publisher: TSMP Records
      Track listing: Sexual rapping / T. Ski Valley -- Sexual instrumental / Glen Adams & Finesse.
    - Catch the beat / T Ski Valley Performed by: T Ski Valley, 1984; SR-258 (Box 5)
      Track listing: Catch the beat (Scratch the beat) -- Catch the beat (Instrumental & breaks)
    - Sexual rapping / T Ski Valley Performed by: T Ski Valley, ca. 1985; SR-259 (Box 5)
      Publisher: Pama
  - LPs - SR 260-310 (Box 6)
    - All I want / Twennynine with Lenny White Performed by: Twennynine, 1981; SR-260 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Elektra/Asylum Records
      Track listing: All I want -- Twennynine (the rap)
    - Bounce, rock, skate, roll: pt 1-2 / Vaughan Mason and Crew Performed by: Vaughan Mason and Crew, 1979; SR-261 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Brunswick Record Corp.
    - Bounce, rock, skate, roll / Vaughan Mason and Crew Performed by: Vaughan Mason and Crew, 1980; SR-262 (Box 6)
      Track listing: Roller skate -- Cravin' your body -- Thinking about you baby -- We're gonna funk you up -- Bounce, rock, skate, roll I -- Bounce, rock, skate, roll II.
    - Invasion of the spacepeckers / Videokids Performed by: VideoKids, 1984; SR-263 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Break Records
      Track listing: Do the rap -- Cartooney tunes (incl. Happy Birthday) -- La Bamba -- I'm a rock and roll pecker -- Communication outerspace -- Woodpeckers from space -- Gimmi that banana -- Do you like surfing -- Skyrider.
    - Let's B-B break Performed by: Weeks & Co, 1984; SR-264 (Box 6)
      Track listing: Let's B-B break -- Let's B-B break (short version) -- Let's B-B break (instrumental).
    - Beat wave Performed by: Warp 9, 1983; SR-265 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Prism
      Track listing: Beat wave -- Beat wave (dub version)
    - Haunted house of rock Performed by: Whodini, 1983; SR-266 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Jive
      Track listing: The haunted house of rock (extended version) -- The haunted house of rock (haunted mix) -- The haunted house of rock (vocoder version) -- The haunted house of rock (acapella).
    - Freaks come out at night Performed by: Whodini, 1984; SR-267 (Box 6)
      Track listing: Freaks come out at night -- Grandmaster Dee's haunted scratch -- Five minutes of funk -- Friends.
    - Whodini EP Performed by: Whodini, 1984; SR-268 (Box 6)
      Track listing: Magic's wand -- Nasty lady -- The haunted house of rock -- Rap machine -- It's all in Mr. Magic's wand (Instr.)
    - Big mouth Performed by: Whodini, 1985; SR-269 (Box 6)
      Track listing: Big mouth (beat box mix) -- Big mouth (album mix) -- Big mouth acapella mix).
    - Gunsmoke breakout Performed by: Willesden Dodgers, 1984; SR-270 (Box 6)
      Track listing: Gunsmoke breakout (mix 1) -- Gunsmoke breakout (mix 2).
    - Hey D.J. / The World's Famous Supreme Team Performed by: World's Famous Supreme Team, 1984; SR-271 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Island
      Track listing: Hey D.J. (extended version) -- Hey D.J. (extended instrumental version)
    - Work that sucker to death; Love is on the one / Xavier Performed by: Xavier, 1981; SR-272 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Liberty
      Track listing: Work that sucker to death -- Love is on the one.
    - Step forward Performed by: Prince Jazzbo, 1993; SR-273 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Rastaman
      Track listing: Step forward -- Plum plum -- Jamaican Kallie -- To be free -- Down West -- Crab walking -- Every nigger -- Rock natty -- Down in Babylon -- England cold.
    - Cha-Cha Hogan, Sister Fullbosom & Brother Eatmore Performed by: Humorous sketches; Cha-Cha Hogan, 196ca. 1965; SR-274 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Laff Records
      Track listing: Beat the shit -- The judge -- Drag my balls -- Brother Eatmore -- Spit in -- In the mud -- The nun's balls -- Waving glag -- Miscarriage -- The quarter -- Bettin' Sam -- Tees for balls -- $450 pussy -- Stone cocks***r -- Gramma & grampa -- Zenith -- M & M's -- Sex headache -- Boys town -- Co-signer -- Four seasons -- Appreciation -- Good mornin' -- Funeral parlor -- Chinese laundry -- Alam rag -- Counterfiet $20 bill -- Athletic crotch -- Feelin cooler -- My old gal Sue -- Eight fingered Peggy Malone -- The old Rev. -- Turn a trick -- Hello Dolly -- Got the claps -- Fartin' -- Little prick.
    - Screamin' Jay Hawkins Performed by: Screamin' Jay Hawkins, 1979; SR-275 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Red Lightnin
      Track listing: Not anymore -- Please try to understand -- Baptize me in wine -- This is all -- She put the wammeee -- Well I tried -- You're all of my life to me -- I hear voices -- Talk about me -- Just don't care -- The whammy -- Poor folks -- Your kind of love -- All night -- Monkberry moon delight -- Sweet Ginny.
    - Barnabas in Collins Wood Performed by: Lone Ranger, ca. 1985; SR-276 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Thrill Seekers
      Track listing: Barnabas Collins -- Annie Palmer -- Hell driver -- John Public -- African connection -- Africa -- Frankenstein -- Tribal war -- U.F.O. -- Obeah man -- Two the hard way -- Jamaica weed.
    - Buying a book / Joe Tex Performed by: Joe Tex, vocals; with instrumental ensemble, 1969; SR-277 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Atlantic
      Track listing: We can't sit down now -- Sure is good -- That's the way -- Anything you wanna know -- It ain't sanitary -- The only way -- Grandma Mary -- Get your lies together -- The same things you did to get me -- Buying a book.
    - Revolution will not be televised / Gil Scott-Heron Performed by: Gil Scott-Heron, composer, vocals; Brian Jackson, piano; Ron Carter, Gerry Jemott, double-bass; David Spinozza & Burt Jones, guitars; Hubert Laws, flute and alto saxophone; Eddie Knowles & Charlie Saunders, percussion; Pretty Purdie, drums, 1974; SR-278 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Flying Dutchman
      Track listing: The revolution will not be televised (3:03) -- Sex education: ghetto style (0:48) -- The get out of the ghetto blues (4:59) -- No knock (1:27) -- Lady Day and John Coltrane (3:32) -- Pieces of a man (4:59) -- Home is where the hatred is (3:18) -- Brother (1:42) -- Save the children (4:22) -- Whitey on the moon (1:26) -- Did you hear what they said? (3:25).
    - Daddy's got the mojo / Butterbeans & Susie Performed by: Butterbeans and Susie (Jody and Susie Edwards), with jazz acc, 1989; SR-279 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Swingtime
      Track listing: Kiss me sweet -- Mama stayed out the whole night long -- Construction gang -- A-Z blues -- My daddy's got the mojo, but I got the say-so -- Da da blues -- Gonna make you sorry -- Tain't none of your business -- Been some changes made -- Watch your step -- Gonna start lookin' for a man to treat me right -- Put your mind right on it -- What it takes to bring you back -- Times is hard -- Elevator papa, switchboard mama -- Papa ain't no Santa Claus.
    - Actual voices of ex-slaves telling their experiences to John Henry Faulk: a rare historical recording made nearly 40 years ago Performed by: John Henry Faulk, Laura Smalley, Aunt Harriet Smith (interviewer, interviewees, respectively), 1977; SR-280 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Mark 56 Records
    - Caught up / Millie Jackson Performed by: Millie Jackson, 1974; SR-281 (Box 6)
      Track listing: If loving you is wrong, I don't want to be right -- The rap -- If loving you is wrong, I don't want to be right (reprise) -- All I want is a fighting chance -- I'm tired of hiding -- It's all over but the shouting -- It's easy going -- I'm through trying to prove my love to you -- Summer.
    - Joe Tex spills the beans Performed by: Joe Tex; with vocal and instrumental acc, 1972; SR-282 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Dial
      Track listing: All the heaven a man really needs -- You're sure gonna get it -- Woman stealer -- Rain go away -- Let's go somewhere and talk -- A mother's prayer -- Cat's got her tongue -- Living in the last days -- I come to you -- King Thaddeus -- Trying to win your love -- Papa's dream.
    - Baaad soap / the Supa Duds Performed by: Supa Duds, 1978; SR-283 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Moonglow Records
    - Fever catch it! / Sweet G Performed by: Sweet "G", vocals; with instrumental acc, 1983; SR-284 (Box 6)
      Track listing: Games people play (vocal) -- Games people play (instrumental)
    - Astrology rap; Star power Performed by: Fredrick Davies and Lewis Anton, 1980; SR-285 (Box 6)